Let's start with another big news from Express
and that is about the insurance sector.
Our correspondent Anubhav is with us
who has a very deep grip on the insurance sector.
Some big developments are taking place.
Yes, these
can be big developments for our dear policyholders.
Insurance companies believe that in the
GST Council meeting that will be held in March, the
announcement that will be made there will be a reduction in the
medical mediclaim health insurance. Whatever
premium is paid on health insurance, it is 18 per cent.
Insurance companies have full confidence in this and there is a
rationale behind this too. They want to put a question mark on
GST that Redmi is good, its son is National
and this will not cause much loss to the government in taxes
because as we have
seen in our survey that the demand for health insurance has
increased. If our health
insurance is clean and the
flame of Rs 13000 crore has come to the insurance companies,
health insurance claims have been taken in more than nine lakh queries
and after that, if I
talk about the analysis of January, then the premium
of the overall industry as compared to January last year is
20% is big, 100%
increase has happened and 18 per cent itself seems to be tasty, so
this further penetration which is to be
increased in insurance is being driven by an Indian, that is why
I am also demanding that there should be 18 per
cent because it is a very
important thing to protect the people,
so this 18 per cent should be increased, Reddy and General
Insurance Council's demand is for five buttons
but it is expected that if
Agni becomes 12 per cent and the 20 per
cent which is happening now and it becomes 30-35 per
cent then there will be no loss in tax to the government,
there will be Remedy Newton
because the volume will increase so there will be
no loss in tax, so it will be
good news for the insurance companies, the
way there is a growth of 20 per cent today and
there GST is reduced, so right now you go to buy a policy and
you are
paying the premium there, then you have to pay
around ₹2000, so
if GST is there then
if people buy insurance then the
companies will get higher premium  And the
government also benefits, so it is
possible to increase the percentage from 5 percent,
if it happens then the demand is 25 percent,
but if you consider the collection side also, it should be
12 percent and the next grade will be, if
these stories turn out to be true and the next gym happens
then I will cut you a welding, Ghaghra
boys, we also used to have news of medical not being able to, the
second thing was not talking about, some
loss in January was there, if
inside the insurance, if they are confirming it in the
finance ministry, if someone is
saying that it will come and
deepen at the higher level in IRDA, then attached with two big emphasis,
modern, the next day there are big papers of the country,
they did it, then further their people in the country were
saying
that with management control, it is
very important, health insurance is a
big thing, it is important, there is no
loss at all, your percentage is very high,
many people do not get it done,
I have definitely taken action this month,
now see, the latest problem there is that
in January the health insurance premium of the overall industry
added  20 percent
bigger than the previous one I will definitely give it. Okay, whenever there
is an 18 year GST, then if it increases from 30 to 35
percent and there is a traditional tax, then the
government has not suffered any loss in tax. And if
this comes to the government, then
more people will come under the ambit of insurance, then
you will not have to
spend on medical infrastructure.
From hospital to infrared,
this is the welfare state's responsibility in front of other types.
Once this
is the case, then let us tell you this, the gallon card will
not be understood. So I will tell our viewers that
whoever did good work,
we will keep them here for the whole decade.
Absolutely, there is pressure on those who did good work in
medical insurance, New India Assurance,
this kind of thing, be sure,
after all, I think that this is very good
positive news for the entire insurance
sector and whenever the government talks about
increasing the base, I like it
very much. I want that the same should be done
for tax and the country should be
expanded like insurance.  The company is
saying that if there is a shortage of notes, it will
cost a little less and you will be
able to check your health by locking it. In India, we
alone talk about India being a country full of
under-insured countries, so that is no doubt a very
good step. Now, it is wrong that all the general
insurance companies are ICICI
Lombard or General Insurance, but any
other company is very good for Sony SAB
and we are seeing a hold. If it
starts spying on the pack, then this is a very welcome step, it is
very good for the industry
and I would also like that there should be intrusion somewhere for life insurance
because there are many people here
who do not have land, so a very
important thing is term insurance because
Pankaj Future is
Monday, it depends on whether
they get a security somewhere and so this is
very good for the inch on the fog and
very good for all individuals, so those who
want to buy inch open or those who
buy, their time to exit will be
less. Welcome test is a very good thing, it is a
small step and a good development. We hope
that it will be here soon.
Seen action coming soon and insurance tops are gaining momentum because of this, I will
take it
in the best section only.